He seems to be the happiest.
He's that supportive.
Dad and Mom are grinning so much at the 66's, too.
They're grinning like crazy.
I couldn't see their mouths because of the mask.
Dad is especially crying.
Just like that.
Dad.
After it's over.
We're...
He's kind of hot around here.
I was thinking, "What's with this guy?
Dad...
Uncle
I'm Sabapong's father.
He's like...
I'm always watching you
Thank you for your help
I feel like I've met the master
Mom's rather shy maybe
She seems calm.
Is she?
It's the opposite of what I imagined.
I thought you were more like...
At home, yes.
At home, she's like, "Thanks.
You're a valedictorian at home.
Thanks!
No, thank you. Oh, no.
Oh, my God.
Anyway...
I was just saying how grateful I am for your parents.
Now...
I'm really...
They've come to see us perform.
They came to see the concert.
I was just saying how grateful I am.
You were saying that, weren't you?
Let him know.
By the way...
By the way... parents...
Do they come to Ev-chan's live performances?
Yes, they do.
If it's at a venue nearby...
If it's a venue nearby, they come on their days off.
Quite a bit.
By the way...
What are the fathers and mothers like in Iwakoya?
I mean...
What's it like to be a member of the Iwakoya family?
Well...
I don't know...
I don't know, I just have this image of them.
What kind of image?
Look at their faces.
Everyone's smiling at you.
Everyone is talking about random things.
They're all talking about random things, and they're all saying the same thing. They all put in the appropriate synonyms.
like "wow".
That's the image I had in mind.
But that's just an image.
But the mother is rather...
She's also a mother.
But she's more like a big sister.
Those sisters...
Uh...
I'm an only child.
So in that sense, we're really close.
That's right.
The handcuffs aren't very good.
Fathers and mothers in this age group
and mothers in this age group are like friends.
A little.
They don't feel like a father and son.
Your father...
He's kind of funny, too.
I don't know...
I'm having trouble deciding what's interesting.
What do you mean?
Like, "Yo!
That's not what I meant.
I don't know.
It's like...
Like a war.
Like, "Dad, please take care of your son.
Like a comedy family
No, no, no, I didn't mean it like that. No, no, no, that's not what I meant.
But...
You like fashion.
Oh, really?
At any rate, I like fashion.
Then you're very modern.
I complained to your father about one thing.
Oh?
So...
Use this phone.
Oh, my God.
I can see it in your eyes.
But maybe...
I feel like I should just tell you in person.
I'm probably looking.
I want you to give me a line.
Oh.
Ignore?
No, he doesn't have the app.
It's LINE.
Oh, wow.
I didn't know they didn't put it in nowadays.
I don't know.
I've always wanted to be in a LINE group.
I've always wanted to be in a family LINE group.
Really?
I guess that's normal for other people.
I guess it's normal for other people.
Well, you've been doing it for a while.I was doing so-so, I guess.
But I don't think it was your father who was doing it.
I mean, it's not like my dad was doing it.
It's on the iPhone.
It's an app.
I'm using an app to do it with my dad.
Oh.
That's why I can't create a LINE group family LINE group.
I can't group them together.
So I have to go to the trouble of sending this to both of them.
I see.
It's a bit of a hassle.
So I asked him to let me in.
I wonder if your father can't join for some reason.
Because there's no one else to do it.
Oh, no...
No way.
Because there's no one else to do it.
He went to a lot of trouble to let her in, didn't he?
Of course... but you don't have to do it just for Emma.
That's right.
Dad... it's not for me to say, but...
Even I'm on LINE.
That's right.
I'm the helicopter of the world.
The helicopter of the world.
helicopter
Helicopter of the edge of the world
The edge of the world
and even I'm in a place where I'm about to fall a little more.And even I'm in a place where I'm about to fall a little more, so...
Dad, why don't you just let it in for now?
That's right.
He's a veteran. He can delete it right away.
So you've been using an iPhone 7 or 6 until recently?
Yeah.
I've been using a fossilized version of that thing.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Fossilized.
It's pretty old.
It's still around, you know, the one with the home button.
Wow.
It's kinda cool.
I like it.
It's so cool.
I want one now.
My first phone, by the way, was a 6.
Yeah.
I still have a picture of it.
Yes, I still have it.
It's something.
That's right.
It's all shattered, but the screen...
The home button is nice.
The home button is nice, isn't it?
It's like the good old days when you could just press it.
It's nostalgic.
I used to press it all the time.
I used to press it all the time, but now it's gone. We were pushing it around, but now it's gone.
It's all gone now.
Well, I guess it's true... some mothers do it on line or something.
She does.
And your father, too, even though he's not on LINE.
That's right.
They don't charge me any money.
Just peek at him and he'll peek at you.
While saying that, maybe your father will take the opportunity to put it in today.
Yes.
And then he'd get all worked up about it.
I love it.
Yes.
It's like...
I don't know what I'm going to do.
I'm obsessing over it.
I wonder what kind of pictures they take.
He sends me a lot of stamps I don't know.
I already paid for the stamps.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah...
He's probably a small prize winner.
He'll definitely send me something.
You're right, he's a little deprived.
Yeah, yeah.
That's how it is, isn't it?
Okay.
Well, let's start the recording again today.
Okay. Yes, sir.
that is to say
Yes, sir.
Then, I would like to go.
Yes, that's why.
I've been working on it all week.
There was one thing that came to mind.
By the way...
You haven't done that thing yet, have you?
You know...
Speaking of him...
I'm sure...
That's his mark.
That's right.
It's not enough.
I'm feeling a little itchy.
Of course it is.
Or...
It's like...
Like...
Like that.
That's right.
Then, everyone in front of the TV...
I'm looking forward to seeing you all.
Let's wrap up the week together.
Okay.
Then, please join us.
All of you, please join us.
Let's do it!
Gandalfire!Gandalfire
Yay!
That's good.
This is it. This is it.
I'm gonna be stuck on this all week.
It's this one.
Like, Merry Christmas.
I'm trapped.
Well, well, well.
That's how it's going to be.
However... however...
And this Kannai Devil, too.
I'm steadily working on starting up a new section
I've been working on it.
Masked Liar
I'm thinking of starting a new section
I'm thinking of starting a new section called "Masked Liar
It hasn't started yet.
But I'm working on it under the radar.
I'd like to hear from you, the viewers.
If you have any ideas, please send them to me.
Well, well, well.
Really?
By the way, that masked liar...
Of course, he's a hero.
Isn't the costume important?
It's important.
I asked him to design it himself.
And here's what I came up with.And here's what we came up with.
This is it
this
This one
I'm already wondering if everything will be all right.
I'm already wondering if everything will be okay.
I have to wear it.
How did it come to this?
I wanted to make a symbol of a hero wishing for peace.
I wanted to make a peace mark, but I don't have the drawing ability.
This is a little perverted!
When he first came out, the place was in an uproar and everyone left.
Some people even got angry and said, "Enough of this!
Some people even started to get angry at me, like, "Enough of this!
Thank you very much.
First of all, I'd like to see an image of Mishima City.
Wow, that's good...
This is the base No.
Hey, hey, hey, stiff!
I'm a little stiff...
You don't do that, do you?
I know, that's what this is, that's what this is, that's who's hands are on this, that's what happens when you make it real, right?
It's pretty horrifying.
I'm sure it's not horrifying.
And... a and...
I wrote the popular Kamen Raier... who's usually a fresh-faced clunker... but is actually a righteous rider... and it's really good!I tried to write a story about a popular masked rider who's usually a fresh-faced clunker, but is actually a righteous rider.
I'm not sure if this is how it's going to turn out, but I'm sure it's going to be good.
I don't know right now, but maybe this is how it's going to turn out.
I'd like you to go to the location corner as Mr. Oyasama... where the real Kamen Rider also goes to a coffee shop...
The real Kamen Rider also has a scene in a coffee shop where the master of the coffee shop, Otoya-san, and the rider have a discussion.
And also, thank you for writing about it at the Nipporini Review Place.
Thank you for writing about it in the Dancing Nipporini review site.
I wrote the first hero masked rider at the YT level!
He is kind-hearted, always smiling, and does not attack without reason, even if it's an enemy.
If you refuse to shake hands with me, I'll kick you in the face with a "lame" kick... and if you say, "That's a little harsh," I'll just say, "Hey, that's a little harsh.
Hey, that's lame!
I'm not going to be violent just because someone refuses to shake my hand.
I'm just trying to get a good look at you
I still wanted to write this!
I'm not sure why... but I'm not sure if this is what I meant or not...
It's just like this.
I'm just trying to write it down.
I've tried to write it.
First of all, let's have a look at them.
The year 2000XX A.D.
The Devil Master suddenly appears...
And then... Gunbundari took this...
Oh, oh, oh!
With my next blow, I will bury all of you human beings.
Sounds villainous.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Oh, my God.
Great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great.
Great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great.
The police, the military, the human race's means of resistance...The police, the military, all means of human resistance...
The earth was about to end.
Oh, no.
We are left with no choice but to perish.
And help us... we have one last hope... and it's called...
Help me, no wall!
What's going to happen now?
I will keep the peace on Earth.
Oh...
Hmm...
Shin.
Masked Liar!
And...
It glowed.
I did something weird
And what a surprise
It's gone!
Mankind was saved by hiding it.
What are you doing here?
Watch and drink.
You're right.
You're not a rider?
Hey, Dad...
Why does he have his nose in his head?
I'm sure he's been through a lot.
It's not a good one.
What's this?
It's a big letdown.
It's a letdown.
Interesting.Interesting.
I like it.
This is what you get when you reproduce it exactly as it is.
It's a faithful reproduction.
It's amazing!
And they came up with the goods.
Amazing!
Amazing.
A helmet and a Kamen Liar transformation set.
A helmet and a belt.
Three pages addressed to my father.
Wow.
A set to transform into...
Wow, wow, wow.
Helmet and belt, addressed to father
This is how you do it.
Here, like this.
I put it on.
It can't be helped... it was written by the author.
I wrote it.
Let's go get some goods or something.
It's funny.
It's really funny.
But just in case... a Liar tee shirt and a Liar bandana...
Oh, my God!
That's great.
That's what I want to see, too.
That's so cool!
Short-sleeved T-shirts are awesome.
It's like, "I've got this all over the place.They say this is thoroughly in place.
I'm sure.
It's insanely good.
I want one.
I'd love it.
It's a woge.
I love the transformation.
It's like this.
I'm like this.
Bashan.
Oh, my God.
Interesting. Really. Thank you.
Well, well, well, well, well.
You know what else?
Liar is, of course, a friend of justice.
But he's also a good mimic.
So, just in case...
Yuukiku from Zatar sent this.
Kashiwa City, Chiba Prefecture
The other day, as I was walking home after dark.
I was on my way home when I felt something looking at me.
I turned my eyes in that direction.
I saw a praying mantis glaring at me.
So, I would like you to be my best friend, Mr. Sawapon.
I'd like you to be our hero and give us your impression.
I'd appreciate it if you could give me your feedback.
Okay, so this is what it looks like.
Wow, wow, wow.
Is it weird?
Why is it brown? Why is it brown?
Isn't it green?
Isn't it usually green?
Even the color. Even the color.
When the mantis molts...
They turn brown.
Yes, that's right.
They change color, too.
It's true, they're usually green.
Really? Your eyes are meeting mine.
Amazing, for such a little guy.
Mantis don't scare me at all.
He's got motive.
He doesn't run away so easily. He's so big.
To a praying mantis, I'm the size of a 15-meter giant!
That's right.
I'm a belt-loader!
Even though I'm here like this...
I don't know... Like...
What the hell?
Amazing!
He's not running away at all!
No, he's just being stubborn.
You mantis have a lot of guts.
Really...
Yes, well, well, well, well...
Thank you very much.
Well, well, well...
Let's continue... To be continued...
If you can think of anything related to Liar
Anything you can think of that's related to Liar?
Yes, I would love to.
Maybe a scenario.
I'd like it.
I was thinking that's the kind of story I'd like to see.
It's interesting that most of them were like that.
"Out, out, out.
Like, "He's out. He's out. He's a pervert.
It's cool until then.
Well, well, well...
Well, that's that.
Well, then... I guess it's time to start the live broadcast.
Yes.
The live broadcast is over.
Well, today, I started my shift at Gambanna this week.
The first thing he said was, "Isn't Christmas coming soon?
That's right.
Well, I started this week.
Yes.
I thought, "What the heck, that's early." But then I realized it's not that early.
That's already the case.
Considering it's on the air...
Yes, that's right.
You know...
It's called bullying in America.
Thanks to
Yes, sir. Yes, sir.
Pirari is also a Ghost.
In sé
Yes, sir.
And this one
Lonrath.
That's right.
Yes, sir.
Yes, ma'am.
The on-air...
This is what they say.
There is no way
This is what
on the internet
It's funny, isn't it?
It's Watai.
Well...
I'll ask the actress if she'd like to pay her respects.
Gone is the bedrock, you know?
I'd like to say Merry Christmas to you anyway.
I've learned to turn once before I say it.
So please join us.
Let's turn, come on, turn, please turn with me.
"Let's go around together" "Let's go around together" "Let's go around together" "Let's go around together
It's almost Christmas, isn't it?
What do you think?
It's bursting, isn't it? Wow! I can't tell when it started and when it ended.
It's the kind of thing you get into a habit of.It's the kind of feeling you get into when you're in the mood for something habit-forming.
I'll see you next week. Thank you very much again for this week.
Thank you very much.